Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(تَوأَم)
(Episode 19)
(الحلقة 19)
Your Highness, he is here.
صاحب السمو، هو هنا.
And the good show begins.
ويبدأ العرض الجيد.
Lu Zhao!
لو تشاو!
Attack!
هجوم!
Back then, I could not save Miao He.
في ذلك الوقت، لم أتمكن من إنقاذ مياو هي.
So I know better than anyone...
لذا فأنا أعرف أفضل من أي شخص آخر...
that kind of heart-wrenching pain.
هذا النوع من الألم المؤلم.
You are luckier than me.
أنت أكثر حظا مني.
You have a choice.
لديك خيار.
Are you going to watch him die in front of you?
هل ستشاهده يموت أمامك؟
Look.
ينظر.
Does he not look like you did on the day you were surrounded?
هل لا يبدو كما كنت في اليوم الذي حاصروك فيه؟
You two are indeed the same.
أنتم الاثنان نفس الشيء بالفعل.
Knowing it is a dead end,
مع العلم أنه طريق مسدود،
yet you never turned back.
ولكنك لم ترجع أبدًا.
Since you are not willing to cooperate with me,
نظرًا لأنك غير راغب في التعاون معي،
I will...
أنا سوف...
invite you to watch...
ندعوك لمشاهدة...
the death of a cornered beast.
موت الوحش المحاصر.
If he dies,
إذا مات،
you will never get the Defense Map!
لن تحصل على خريطة الدفاع أبدًا!
Xiao Ren.
شياو رن.
Do you want to see her die before you?
هل تريد رؤيتها تموت قبلك؟
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
I will take you home.
سوف آخذك إلى المنزل.
Xiao Ren!
شياو رن!
Kneel down!
اركع!
Cut off your right arm.
اقطع ذراعك اليمنى.
Then I shall spare her.
ثم سأوفرها.
Situ Xing Yuan,
الموقع شينغ يوان,
I want you dead!
أريدك ميتا!
Golden Silk Armor!
درع الحرير الذهبي!
Stop them!
اوقفوهم!
Cover Master!
غلاف ماستر!
Does Xuntian Sect wish for mutual destruction?
هل ترغب طائفة شونتيان في الدمار المتبادل؟
Retreat!
تراجع!
So it is him.
فهو كذلك.
(Xuntian Sect)
(طائفة شونتيان)
What is going on?
ما الذي يجري؟
He has been injured worse than this before.
لقد أصيب بجروح أسوأ من هذا من قبل.
What happened this time?
ماذا حدث هذه المرة؟
And why is he in so much pain?
ولماذا هو في هذا القدر من الألم؟
He cannot feel pain, can he?
إنه لا يستطيع أن يشعر بالألم، أليس كذلك؟
Speak!
يتكلم!
The poison Situ Xian gave you...
السم الذي أعطاك إياه سيتو شيان...
had no antidote.
لم يكن له ترياق.
To save you, Master personally...
لإنقاذك يا سيدي شخصيًا...
Personally what?
شخصيا ماذا؟
He personally cut out the Golden Silkworm from his heart.
لقد قام شخصيا بقطع دودة القز الذهبية من قلبه.
That is how he cured you...
هكذا شفاك...
of the heart-piercing poison.
من السم الذي يخترق القلب.
Removing the silkworm from his heart nearly killed him.
إزالة دودة القز من قلبه كاد أن يقتله.
But if that were all,
ولكن لو كان هذا كل شيء،
it would not be this serious.
لن يكون الأمر بهذه الخطورة.
- Shao Yao! - Ling Su.
- شاو ياو! - لينغ سو.
We cannot hide it.
لا يمكننا إخفاء ذلك.
Have you still not realized who it is...
هل لم تدرك بعد من هو...؟
that stands before you?
الذي يقف أمامك؟
Since Master is here,
بما أن السيد هنا،
Ling Su dares not conceal it.
لينغ سو لا يجرؤ على إخفاء ذلك.
You died unexpectedly before this.
لقد مت بشكل غير متوقع قبل هذا.
To save you, Chief resorted to witchcraft.
لإنقاذك، لجأ الزعيم إلى السحر.
He went against heaven's will,
لقد ذهب ضد إرادة السماء،
trading one life for another.
تبادل حياة بأخرى.
This...
هذا...
is the price.
هو السعر.
Trading...
تجارة...
Trading one life...
تداول حياة واحدة...
for another?
لآخر؟
This act defies the laws of nature.
هذا الفعل يخالف قوانين الطبيعة.
You must sacrifice half your life...
يجب عليك التضحية بنصف حياتك...
for a chance to bring her back to life.
للحصول على فرصة لإعادتها إلى الحياة.
If it could bring back my sister,
لو كان بإمكانه إعادة أختي،
so what if I must go to the underworld?
فماذا لو كان يجب علي أن أذهب إلى العالم السفلي؟
You may go back.
يمكنك العودة .
Go back.
عُد.
Why are you so foolish?
لماذا أنت غبي هكذا؟
Sis.
أخت.
I am here.
أنا هنا.
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
You are all right.
أنت بخير.
You are still calling me Lu Zhao?
هل مازلت تناديني لو تشاو؟
Stop teasing me.
توقف عن مضايقتي.
I am back.
أنا عدت مرة أخرى.
It is me, Xiao Ren.
إنه أنا، شياو رين.
Sis is back.
لقد عادت أختي.
You are back.
لقد عدت.
If I had not come back,
لو لم أعود،
how would I have known...
كيف كنت سأعرف...
that you sacrificed your fate,
أنك ضحيت بمصيرك،
harmed your heart,
أذى قلبك،
and hid so much from me?
وأخفى عني الكثير؟
Sis.
أخت.
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
I... I was too scared.
أنا.. كنت خائفة جدًا.
I... I was too anxious.
أنا... كنت قلقًا جدًا.
Please do not abandon me.
من فضلك لا تتركني.
How can I accept what you have done?
كيف يمكنني أن أقبل ما فعلته؟
This is your life!
هذه حياتك!
Is it worth it?
هل يستحق ذلك؟
If I can trade half my life...
إذا كان بإمكاني أن أتاجر بنصف حياتي...
to bring you back,
لأعيدك،
that is the greatest gift for me.
هذه أعظم هدية بالنسبة لي.
Without the Golden Silkworm,
بدون دودة القز الذهبية،
does it hurt a lot?
هل يؤلمني كثيرا؟
No, it does not.
لا، لا يفعل.
Xiao Ren.
شياو رن.
Let us get married.
دعونا نتزوج.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I will never leave you alone again.
لن أتركك وحدك مرة أخرى أبدًا.
All right.
حسنًا.